I'm invoking our Body Snatchers clause.
The Body Snatchers clause requires me
to help destroy someone we know...
(Leonard:)...who's been replaced with an alien pod.
(Sheldon:)Yes. She's in the living room.
Go. I'll wait here.
- Sheldon, what are you doing out of bed?
- Now. Do it.
You need your sleep for your cognitive
processing to perform at optimum levels.
(Ramona:)- Now, come on.
- Godzilla clause?
LEONARD:
Not unless she destroys Tokyo.
SHELDON:
Rats.
I've got it!
(Sheldon(excitedly):)I finally reconciled
the black hole information paradox...
(Sheldon(excitedly):)...with my theory
of string-network condensates.
- It's unbelievable. It's paradigm-altering.
- And I could not have done it without you.
(Ramona:)- I just offered a little encouragement.
- You did a lot more than that.
(Sheldon:)You helped me work out
the masses of the fermions...
...and you pumiced my hammertoe.
(Sheldon:)How can I ever repay you?
(Ramona:)Well, would you consider naming it
the Cooper-Nowitzki Theorem?